Sarah Marshall

Goal focused and principled individual with extensive experience in guest services and administrative duties. Organized and motivated team player who utilizes strong interpersonal and technological skills. Recognized by managers as a hardworking, dedicated individual with the undeniable ability to excel.



sr70079@gmail.com



519 Moser Road King, NC 27021



(336) 403-7330



linkedin.com/in/sarah-marshall-



User... 35%

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - CHAPEL HILL CODING BOOTCAMP

NOVEMEBER 2020 - MAY 2021

Full Stack Web Developer Certification

CAPE FEAR COMMUNITY COLLEGE

MAY 2010

Associate of Arts

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARSHALL HOUSEHOLD - CHIEF HOME OFFICER

October 2018 - April 2021

Use excellent organizational skills while managing a constantly fluctuating schedule and creating a daily routine

Budget management

Delegating tasks within the workplace

Utilize on the spot creative problem solving

Excellent communication

AMERICAN AIRLINES - FLIGHT ATTENDANT

April 2015 - October 2018

Set a high standard for consistent in-flight service that includes serving meal/beverages and selling onboard products

Handled a wide variety of situations while in continuous contact with the public

Worked independently or as part of a team without supervision

Ensured the safety and comfort of passengers

Provided leadership by responding to a variety of emergency and non-emergency situations Worked in climates and locations across the globe and worked variable shifts

INVESTIGATIVE ASSOCIATES AND CONSULTANTS - RESEARCH CONSULTANT

May 2014 - April 2015

Performed comprehensive background investigations of clients' employment applicants from a variety of agencies using investigative tools; compiled reports on individuals in question; maintained records on investigations

Assisted in drug screening processes and procedures

Performed fee calculations for applicants

Demonstrated continuous efforts to improve operations, decrease turnaround times, streamline work processes and work cooperatively and jointly to provide quality customer service Projected an outgoing professional personality

DISNEYLAND RESORT - COLLEGE PROGRAM INTERN

August 2011 - January 2012

Part of a multifunctional team in a food and beverage location that is ranked as one of the busiest fast-food restaurant in the world

Delivered exceptional guest services daily in a high-volume area

Maintained ability to manage multiple tasks and work well under pressure

Made lifelong memories to families and guests who visited the park from around the world

HOBBIES AND INTEREST











Reading

Board Games

Camping

Movies

Gryffindor